I have twelve hundred
I count a Chevette and twelve days to set up the business
haha
on tane
all good
is what they do
is there OR do not have
I just placed 1 order here in the graphic
said it's ready tomorrow
you know that little blue ribbon
I on your website I am looking for 1
then like one day you think you're ready
the next one for me makes a hundred and fifty in the money
fucking brother
50 uncle box
1 more delivery now
3 boxes
please
oi oi
it's marcel speaks
delivery
repair
ha ha Caio pleasure
all great
I'm fine so you asked for the repair
caramba cara
I went to deliver it here to the zs and Camile said
ah i want a box too
I just sent you the pix because here is the QR code
she paid and already sold one to her
thank you from the heart man
man I'm bothering a lot with Instagram messages
there from the Passenger's workshop
because i have to deliver
and then I have to drive and then there's the production
oh there is so much
is on
I don't know if you go through this
but the enterprising self is very difficult cé do everything knows
guy i came to deliver bro
market
I'm not locating
the person i had to deliver
down here there are several stores
I don't remember the person's name
if she paid
getting crazy in here guy with the demands
look at the time
that I'm losing because I'm not having organization
in my business
that's a lot in the head to take care of
and i'm being really dumb
because i'm trying to grow up and i'm not having
organization
I'm here,
I don't know,
twenty minutes
that you might be in demand if you have no sale
I'm making the deliveries
tô demand
but physically I'm getting exhausted
bro that's not passive income
is active income
I bring 1 box of 15reais and pay 16 parking
cannon speaks
and then brother
how come your time is better now
in a quagmire here
mano I'm making some deliveries here
I'm not able to answer the message
needed 1 help from you that's 1 very creative guy
and understands from the stop
has a tool
I think it's the easiest to use
it's called gpt maker and you can create
you will define there
what is the Passenger price
what is the delivery format like
and she will serve her customers alone
it's the cheapest scenario you'll get
hire
ok it's us I'll deliver here
the time has come to set the playground on fire again
until tomorrow